{"questions":[{"question":"The prize competition was ____ as a showcase for new technology, but instead the competition was marred by disqualifications and disputes.","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"disappointing"},{"key":"B","answer":"conceived"},{"key":"C","answer":"touted"},{"key":"D","answer":"heralded"},{"key":"E","answer":"promising"},{"key":"F","answer":"required"}],"multiple":true,"right":["C","D"]},{"question":"The new institute provides intensive postgraduate teaching to a wide range of students, in the hope that these students will use their knowledge to boost the country's ____ economy.","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"languishing"},{"key":"B","answer":"emerging"},{"key":"C","answer":"booming"},{"key":"D","answer":"domestic"},{"key":"E","answer":"bankrupt"},{"key":"F","answer":"flagging"}],"multiple":true,"right":["A","F"]},{"question":"Like other metaphors, the \"book of Nature\" has two facets: it is ____ but if taken literally, it may mislead.","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"heuristic"},{"key":"B","answer":"perceptive"},{"key":"C","answer":"poetic"},{"key":"D","answer":"insightful"},{"key":"E","answer":"prosaic"},{"key":"F","answer":"iconoclastic"}],"multiple":true,"right":["B","D"]},{"question":"The increasing interactivity emerging in the latest computer systems means that the traditional view of the computer as a _______ of information now unduly limiting.","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"gleaner"},{"key":"B","answer":"transformer"},{"key":"C","answer":"processor"},{"key":"D","answer":"producer"},{"key":"E","answer":"repository"},{"key":"F","answer":"cache"}],"multiple":true,"right":["E","F"]},{"question":"Turing’s life exerts a powerful and ____ effect on writers – the combination of the highly intellectual and the personally dramatic is hard to resist","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"abiding"},{"key":"B","answer":"pervasive"},{"key":"C","answer":"perennial"},{"key":"D","answer":"irresistible"},{"key":"E","answer":"unmitigated"},{"key":"F","answer":"multifaceted"}],"multiple":true,"right":["A","C"]},{"question":"As a result of his regimented upbringing, that left him unable to see the nuances of complex situations, he was often accused of being ____ .","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"indecisive"},{"key":"B","answer":"tyrannical"},{"key":"C","answer":"obtuse"},{"key":"D","answer":"boorish"},{"key":"E","answer":"xenophobic"},{"key":"F","answer":"imperceptive"}],"multiple":true,"right":["C","F"]},{"question":"It is paradoxical that String Theory inspires such widespread respect when it is so ____ that few could ever hope to master its claims.","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"intractable"},{"key":"B","answer":"confusing"},{"key":"C","answer":"elevated"},{"key":"D","answer":"arcane"},{"key":"E","answer":"obscure"},{"key":"F","answer":"rigorous"}],"multiple":true,"right":["D","E"]},{"question":"Those with a reputation for ____ behavior seldom inspire respect: unwavering adherence to a viewpoint is more admired than flexibility.","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"capricious"},{"key":"B","answer":"bombastic"},{"key":"C","answer":"dogmatic"},{"key":"D","answer":"fickle"},{"key":"E","answer":"honorable"},{"key":"F","answer":"stalwart"}],"multiple":true,"right":["A","D"]},{"question":"The courtiers of the time had to be ____ in order to survive in an atmosphere where the least sign of rebellion could lead to banishment or worse.","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"taciturn"},{"key":"B","answer":"fawning"},{"key":"C","answer":"docile"},{"key":"D","answer":"self-serving"},{"key":"E","answer":"upright"},{"key":"F","answer":"servile"}],"multiple":true,"right":["B","F"]},{"question":"Forgiveness was fine in theory, but she had trouble in accepting a religion that would allow ____ evildoers access to heaven.","options":[{"key":"A","answer":"repentant"},{"key":"B","answer":"contrite"},{"key":"C","answer":"blatant"},{"key":"D","answer":"venial"},{"key":"E","answer":"pardoned"},{"key":"F","answer":"recalcitrant"}],"multiple":true,"right":["A","B"]}],"parent":[]}